No living creature was hurt
during the production of this film.
Visit our website for more: turkision.com
You are a demon, Ismihan!
You are a demon! A demon!
I did not do anything to you!
No one will believe this slander!
You will drown in the blood of the
innocent people you murdered!
Even though I killed Esma,
and caused this wound...
...this dagger...
...is yours, Malhun.
I have witnesses, too.
Take her!
I have witnesses.
Right, Bengi Hatun?
I haven't seen anything.
Anything.
Get up!
I said get up Bengi!
Esma tried to kill me.
And she failed.
So I killed her.
What have you done?
Esma was so young.
Esma was my daughter!
Esma failed. So Malhun...
..tried to kill me.
She tried to stab me.
And you saw it.
Celali saw it too.
You will come to the trial..
...and give testimony.
Do you understand me, Bengi?
Esma didn't do anything.
She wouldn’t speak.
You wasted Esma.
She was only going to leave
with her sibling.
I told you.
If you want power, you can't have mercy.
You can't show any weakness Bengi Hatun!
Now go and bury her.
Then come to the trial and
give your testimony.
If you dare to go against me
for that poor girl..
...this time I’ll take your daughter
to whom you gave birth...
..not the one you only raised.
You're a smart woman.
Use your head.
Alps!
We won't stand down
against Ismihan's trap.
She did too much..
...and I don't have any patience left.
I won't let that cruel woman
have my mother!
Everyone get on your horses!
We're going to Sogut. Come on.
Brother.
We're going without consulting anyone.
But father...
When the situation is like this
we can't stand still. No.
Ismihan wants to bring
my mother to the rope.
We can't lose even a moment.
Mother?
Sons..
Mother.
Mother Malhun..
We know. We know it all.
First, we need to be calm.
After I get my mother I can be calm.
Son.
Hold on.
How can I Mother Bala?
Are we going to stand down against
what Ismihan has done?
When did we accept it before
that we would accept it now, Orhan Bey?
Don't worry.
Osman Bey is at Sogut
right now with his alps.
He's doing what’s needed.
I don't want to go against
your word but...
..I can't wait here mother Bala.
It's Osman Bey's order, Orhan Bey.
You and Alaeddin will protect Yenisehir.
As my bey wishes.
Orhan.
Nayman is waiting for us
to leave this place unprotected.
This duty is a hard one.
Don't you see it?
You will protect this place.
I will go ask Bengi about the truth.
She saw everything that happened.
Let's go.
Malhun Hatun did it.
She did!
She made a move on Mother Sultan's life!
She needs to be punished.
A trial should be held!
How could she?
-How could she do this?
-Listen, people!
People who'd do this will have
no mercy on us in the future!
He’s right!
They say Malhun Hatun did this
because of her arrogance.
She should be punished.
She should be.
Even if it's a Bey’s Hatun,
the punishment should be harsh!
He’s right!
She needs to be punished!
We will find out the truth!
We will not leave our Sultan alone!
Let's have a trial and punish her!
Ismihan!
I hope you are not unhappy here, Malhun.
am not, Ismihan.
But when I put you in here, you will be!
You will be crushed beneath
the dreams you have!
You cross the line,
and then you pay the price!
Are you going to make me pay
with slanders?
Look at>that.
Guards.
Malhun Hatun wants to finish
what she left unfinished.
If I wanted to kill you,
you wouldn’t even be able to talk here!
And I would pay the price for it!
You are pitiful, Malhun!
And what's worse is...
...that you thought you could forgive me!
Neither you...
...nor Osman Bey.
You are just grass that I crush under my feet
while I am on the path to power!
You are confusing a
plane tree with grass, Ismihan!
We will see.
Let's see if you will be able to step on us,
or are you going to be crushed under us!?
The humidity here is making Malhun go mad.
She sees impossible .dreams.
Take her out.
Fresh air will be good for her.
Where are you taking me?
You will see.
My Bey, what should we do?
What are your orders?
Wait a second, they riled up the folks.
We will see.
Osman Bey!
Stop.
What’s going on? Malhun Hatun
attempted to kill our Sultan.
Where is your justice?
We trusted your justice!
Calm down. Do you hear what you're saying?
Do you know who you're talking to?
Calm down. Just stop.
What are you doing?
That's not true.
Calm down.
We took precautions, Mother Sultan.
People are gathering.
Good, Karabul.
Good.
My hands are chained.
And your heart's in chains Ismihan.
You're so scared of us.
I don't fear for my life.
I only worry about the future of my state.
Even if...
...a little ant was to
give my state trouble...
...I would fight back.
The future of the state?
Don't fool yourself Ismihan.
You only worry about Osman Bey.
You are..
...so incredibly full of hatred...
...that you work with those
who are Turk's enemies.
Hatun!
Wait Celali. Wait.
Let her speak.
You talk about..
...the state and the future.
But you side with those
who will destroy the state...
..and show no mercy to our children.
And then..
...you claim we're the scapegoat.
Ismihan.
How will you die?
You'll never see it Malhun Hatun.
Because you..
...tried to kill
Mother Sultan of Great Seljuk.
You won't live that long.
See?
Even the people know that
every breath you take from now on...
...is a waste.
Soldiers! Open the gates.
There must be a punishment for murder!
Let me pass.
My Bey.
Let us push through.
Wait.
Let me pass.
Osman!
Osman I'm okay. Don't worry.
Malhun.
Get your sword Osman Bey.
Get it.
Get it so the people can see that you're
made from the same cloth as your hatun.
Don't you feel shame at all?
How can you come to all Seljuk's Mother
Sultan's land without permission like this?
Everyone! Do you see?
If there's someone who's not afraid of Allah
and feeling shame, then it's you, Mother Sultan.
How can you throw my hatun into jail?
Everyone saw it.
Everyone knows what a traitor you are now.
Malhun came here with ill intent
with her spy.
First that assassin Esma...
And when she couldn't do it..
...herself.
Here.
Your hatun’s bloody knife.
She has to pay for it. She has to.
She has to pay.
If she's guilty let her pay for her crimes.
Mother Sultan..
So you've played the biggest move there is huh?
You spilled the blood.
You threw the slander.
Now you're telling me
to wait for the last move.
Tell me.
Where did you see me stop?
Do you think I will let you do this?
Everyone knows your
ill feelings towards me.
Your hatun couldn't help her
anger and made a mistake.
Don't you dare make a move.
Osman Bey.
If not I'll get you trialed
with your hatun.
Mother Sultan.
If I was going to make a move...
...then I would've already destroyed
this place with you in it.
I do everything accordingly and justly.
But you...
...should let go of my hatun
who you detained unjustly.
-If not...
-People...
..look at my wound.
-Get her hanged!
Look at what these rebels have done
to all Seljuk's Mother Sultan.
Now you come here without shame..
...threatening me.
She will pay for it.
Since he’s a bey...
...he wants to be treated differently.
..he wants to be above the law.
Do you see your Osman Bey now?
Is this something that can be done
to Seljuks Sultan?
Even if it's Osman, he's going to
be held accountable!
Mother!
Speak!
What happened?
Who did this to my sister?
I couldn't stop them.
I couldn't stop them...
Ismihan..
Ismihan killed her.
Malhun,.
Malhun was the reason.
They were the reason!
What did Malhun do, mother?
What are you talking about?
Say something, Baybars!
Malhun Hatun sent Esma
to kill Mother Sultan.
Since Esma got caught...
..she tried to kill Mother Sultan herself.
She’s now under arrest.
Malhun Hatun, huh?
I trusted them with my sister!
Malhun wouldn't do that.
Don't you hear them?
Esma died!
Whose side are you on?
Alcicek.
...you're speaking like
you don’t know her.
-Attacking Ismihan-
-Open your eyes, Aktemur!
Your uncle's wife used my sister
to kill Ismihan Sultan!
From now on, both Ismihan Sultan...
...and Malhun Hatun
are our enemies!
Enough!
Don't let your anger blind you.
Don't speak further
until we know the truth.
Quiet.
We have a funeral.
May I, my Bey?
Come in, Kutlu.
Bala Hatun is coming, my Bey.
Also, they're waiting for you
for the funeral stuff.
Alcicek..
...go with Aktemur.
Alcicek!
My condolences.
Well..
..Mother Sultan.
Seems Mother Sultan..
...is preparing a significant sight.
Well..
...when there’s something to see...
...people of course come out to watch.
People!
Truth isn't always laid out in front of us.
The one who dreams
the same thing I dream of!
Don't you...
...make this mistake.
...believe the lies being spoken.
If my hatun is guilty...
...I will punish her myself.
Mother Sultan, you speak of justice!
You are unjust!
The sword I carry is named
"sword of justice!" Now tell me...
...have you ever seen me being...
unjust?
Mother Sultan.
So you are saying that
you are playing this game carefully.
You are saying that you are
so good at being evil, huh?
But when what you did is revealed..
...you will pay for it dearly!
You can’t do anything, Osman Bey!
Because justice is equal to everyone!
Everyone is treated the same way!
Malhun Hatun's trial will
be held today before dusk!
Malhun Hatun will pay for the crimes
she committed against the state...
...and me.
And you, Osman Bey...
...you will kneel before justice!
Justice is for everyone.
I obey the justice.
But only the real one.
Your justice is fake!
You are just playing a game.
And I am going to ruin that!
Malhun.
Don't worry.
Alps.
Come on.
Who brought Esma there, Bengi Hatun?
Tell me.
You called Esma there.
You wanted her to be hushed,
and scare her.
I don't know if you had known
whether she would die or not.
But her blood is not on our hands,
it's on yours.
We did not harm Esma or Ismihan.
Your ambition for power did.
You sacrificed Esma to your nafs
Leave, Bala.
I have nothing else to say.
I have no daughter to lose either.
I see your pain.
I know there’s a mother
inside of you that lives.
I'm not talking to you.
I'm talking to the mother inside you.
Don't let your daughter's killer be free.
Tell the truth in court.
Let's end Ismihan together.
Don't let them keep Malhun away
from her children.
May I come in?
Come in.
Aunt.
They're waiting for the funeral.
Nayman's Base
Don’t! Nayman!
Don't do this!
If I gave you a job...
...you have to do it in time.
You will pay for your stupidity.
Don't!
Great Nayman!
Don't do this!
Great Nayman don’t!
Don't!
carry the parts of catapults
to the carriages.
I won’t build the catapults here.
Osman...
...damaged us by killing the shaman.
What will we do now,
Commander Nayman?
Spirits are angry.
Warriors want blood.
Soon..
...we will wash our swords with
Osman's blood.
We'll water the plants with his blood.
Erlik Han's anger...
...will be felt by all.
We'll finish building the catapults.
Now I need the masters..
...that the Lord is going to send me.
Commander Nayman.
Mother Sultan sent word.
Ismihan arrested Osman's Hatun.
She is trying to put Osman to trouble.
Now it’s my turn.
Erlik Han.
Strengthen my sword with your rage.
I'm going to separate Osman's head
from his body.
From the animals feeding on
Yenisehir land...
..to the kids in their cribs..
...I'm going to kill them all.
Commander Nayman,
The Lord of Bursa is coming.
You'll never be able to build
the catapults Nayman.
Are you trying to
get yourself filled brother?
Bayindir Bey...
Bayindir Bey sent this.
So?
It's from Osman Bey.
The catapults Nayman is getting built
to attack us will be his end.
It's time.
You're going to take the catapults
out of the headquarters tomorrow.
Boran.
Send alps to Yenisehir.
Those who are not there
for security will come with us.
We're going to go to
that Sogut in such a way that...
...we won't let them have Malhun.
We'll get her somehow.
My bey shouldn't we wait for the trail?
Are we going to wait for the trail
Ismihan has created with her slander?
Tell me Boran.
No.
Ismihan's sense of justice...
...has been deceptive,
she only cares for her own gain.
We will get our justice...
...through our own swords.
EyvAllah my bey.
My Bey, she has the people on her side too,
going there...
By turning my people against me,
she wants to tarnish my reputation.
If we stay silent against this...
...then we would be accepting the slander.
That fake trial of hers is hers...
...and the field is ours.
Eyvallah my bey.
These lands are ours.
Ismihan will end too.
Insallah my bey.
But people will know the truth.
Kumral.
With the ahis you're going to
go around the bazaar and all.
The people will learn about all the ill intended things
Ismihan has done until today one by one.
As you wish my bey.
My Bey.
Are we planning a move
against the trial my bey?
We always have a move ready.
Now the people...
...will come closer to the
truth with Kumral Abdal.
And when the trial comes..
...they will see the truth.
Osman.
The rule you've been trying
to accomplish till now...
...is going down with such a
small dagger wound.
Soon.
What do the men
you put to follow Bayindir say?
They're going to tell us if
something important happens, Mother Sultan.
They're keeping their eyes on him.
He left Nayman's headquarters
and went to his shop.
He couldn't find the spy he was talking about
in Nayman's headquarters.
He’s going to use his gold.
Bring him to me after the trial.
Mother Sultan...
...speaking about the trial...
All your efforts can't be simply
to bring Malhun Hatun's death.
At least that's what I think.
Karavul..
...you know they only act on
Osman Bey's orders.
Malhun was simply following his orders.
Once Malhun's guilt is proven...
...Osman will be tried as well.
So the trial is not being held for Malhun...
...it’s being held for Osman.
Mother Sultan..
Bengi Hatun...
What about Bengi Hatun?
What if the Hatun speaks?
Her daughter, her tribe, her life..
There's too much she'd be risking, Celali.
My wrath would always be on her.
Bengi would never cross me.
So you're planning to be
the Mongolian Emperor...
...from this little tent of yours, Nayman...
..and you want me on your side.
You first killed my messengers..
...and now you're here.
You would sacrifice not 3..
..but 3000 of your soldiers..
...to become my ally, Nayman.
What Osman told you was right.
If you're my ally,
you will be Gazhan Han's enemy.
But I already made you my offer.
What you'll get in return will be great.
What is it that you have and I don't?
Things that you've lost.
Byzantines lost a lot of things.
Wouldn't it be nice to get revenge...
...and take back what you've lost?
I'm listening.
I will kill Gazhan Han.
Konya and all borders will be mine.
Konya has been doing poorly
in the hands of the Muslims.
Borders have been suffering
under Osman’s control.
I will let you have all of them.
You will be written as the man
who revived the Byzantines...
...in history.
I've been watching your base
for some time now.
Your soldiers don't like to be here.
Your army is facing poverty.
Do you have the power
to do what you just said?
You're going to give me that power today...
...And I will return the
power to you tomorrow...
...as in food, horses,
weapons and craftsmen
Genghis rewarded the shepherd
who gave him a horse...
...with a thousand horses in return.
There's no one who can give you
what I'm offering.
If Konya and the borderlands are not enough,
Lord Valens.
If you aim for more...
...when everything is over, I will give you an army,
so you can go for Constantinople.
You will be Nayman Khan's friend,
Emperor Valens.
Those who are washed in the blood
should sit on the thrones, Lord.
I thought you were just a warrior, Nayman.
But you are also a
skilled merchant of dreams.
I am happy to be the one
that brings balance to these lands.
But I will think about your offer.
Think about it, Lord Valens.
Give me your answer soon.
I won't share my victory
in a battle I won alone.
There is no victory in these lands
without me, Nayman.
We will meet soon.
Did you make your decision Bengi Hatun?
We are waiting for you to go to the trial.
If I come to that trial..
...Malhun will be sentenced to death.
I am no good for you.
Aunt Malhun is not someone
that would use Ismihan to kill Esma.
If you don't speak,
they will kill aunt Malhun!
You will either talk, or forget about us!
I can't talk, my girl.
For your safety, I can't talk.
May peace and mercy of Allah be upon you.
Oh Allah.
am in Your presence.
I know that You wouldn’t
leave your worshippers alone.
In the name of mother Aysa,
accept my prayers.
Oh Allah.
Save me from this slander.
Redeem Ismihan, who killed an
innocent girl without blinking!
And if she cannot be redeemed..
...allow us to take revenge of the people
who are oppressed by people like Ismihan.
Oh Allah.
My children.
They must be scared now.
Bring peace to their hearts.
Protect them oh Allah.
Ameen.
Oh Allah.
Come on.
Father.
Sons.
My mother says that Bengi Hatun
is not going to speak.
But she will not give up, she says that she will
bring her to the trial no matter what.
My Bey, are we going to wait for Bengi Hatun
to do the right thing for my mother to be free?
We are not going to wait for anyone, son.
Don't worry.
If Bengi Hatun speaks the truth,
it will be for her own good.
If not...
...she will taste my wrath together
with Ismihan.
Alps.
If Bengi Hatun doesn’t speak the truth...
...then our swords...
...will speak it.
As you wish my Bey!
Ismihan..
Your true face will be shown at the trial.
That rope you're trying to
put on our necks...
..will be put on yours.
Come on sons.
My Sultan.
Kumral Abdal and the ahis..
...talk against us to the people.
No matter.
When Bengi Hatun gives her testimony...
...the people will know who Osman
and his Hatun really are.
But...
...we must take precaution.
Karabul.
Increase the watch and the archers.
Place men all around Sogut.
Also the gates of the city.
And especially the gates of the inn.
If Osman dares to try something...
...he will be met with the claw of the lion.
As you wish Mother Sultan.
Celali.
Send a town crier.
The judges should come.
Malhun's trial..
...will be held at court.
Osman will see the people
who are usually by his side...
...against him.
Provoke the people.
As you wish Mother Sultan.
Those who wish to undermine Konya...
...will be erased from
the face of the earth.
Osman.
There won’t be a soul on earth
that remembers you well.
Aktemur Bey and Alcicek Hatun
went to Sogut.
Should we go as we
I have to Aybars.
I'll do whatever that snake wants.
For Alcicek's life.
Time's up Bengi Hatun.
Tell me. Are you with us?
Or with your daughter's killer?
I can't testify for Malhun.
Your eyes say something else.
If I speak...
...Alcicek will die.
I have to do as Ismihan says.
She's not like us. She's the devil.
She’ll kill Alcicek.
She’ll destroy my tribe.
If you don't speak...
...you'll be letting an innocent people perish.
Malhun's innocent like Esma, Bengi.
Think of her kids.
Think of Orhan and Fatma.
No.
I promise you.
I promise we'll protect Alcicek.
She won't be harmed.
Aunt.
Mother Sultan sent a soldier.
They're waiting for you.
They'll take you to the trial.
If Bengi Hatun doesn't show up...
...we'll get Malhun Hatun out of here.
Everyone knows what to do.
Get back to duty.
She has to be punished.
Son.
Don't worry.
This will end today sooner or later.
Allah..
...you help those who are patient.
please help me too, oh Allah
Your trial will be I held. We're going.
People...
...you must be wondering
why the trial is being held here.
I want you all..
...to witness it.
I want the justice to be served
according to the truth.
That rebel Malhun..
..tried to take my
Tried to kill her?
But is this life mine?
no.
I've given up my life
for all of Seljuk anyways.
Is what we heard from Kumral Abdal true?
Will the truth come forward?
Who's telling the truth?
Traitors!
Who’s telling the truth?
Mother Sultan!
Is what Kumral Abdal said true?
Peace be with you.
-Peace be upon you.
They won't make it.
Mother Bala couldn't convince Bengi Hatun.
What will we do father?
Don't worry son.
Nothing will happen to your mother.
Osman.
Malhun..
Mother.
Orhan.
Son.
Hold on now.
Now is not the time.
Are the witnesses here?
Celali is here.
The other witness Bengi Hatun
must be on her way, judge.
The truth will eventually come out, people.
Don't worry.
But keep in mind that...
...the sword that's
swung at us is swung at the State of Seljuk!
We all know what the punishment is.
All we're seeking here is justice.
The judge will decide on..
...the punishment of Malhun Hatun.
In the name of Allah, the Great, the Magnificent...
...the trial now begins.
Speak, Celali. What happened?
I saw everything with my own eyes, judge.
Esma Hatun went for it first.
But after she failed,
Malhun Hatun attacked.
That's what I saw.
Here comes Bengi Hatun,
who also saw everything.
Speak, Bengi Hatun.
Tell the people of Sogpt...
...what Malhun Hatun did.
Just like the Mother Sultan said.,
...I was at the Inn
that day as well.
Esma, who was like a daughter to me,
was there as well.
She was just a little kid
when her mother passed.
I raised her..
...and then I brought her to
Mother Sultan that day.
You don't have to be afraid, Bengi Hatun.
You couldn't have known that
Malhun Hatun was...
...controlling her.
-So, when Esma pulled out her knife...
-Enough!
Stop that venomous tongue of yours!
You're lying!
Esrna didn't do anything to you...
..and you killed her for no reason!
Then you took Malhun's dagger
and stabbed yourself.
-You!
-Judge!
Ismihan threatened to kill my daughter
to stop me from speaking!
You liar!
So they've bought you as well...
Soldiers, arrest her!
What is it Mother Sultan?
Are you unhappy with the truth?
Is Bengi Hatun not speaking
the things you wanted her to say?
Dear Judge!
If there is a traitor here..
...it’s right in front of you!
She is a traitor that sold
her state to the Mongolians!
So you are making plans against me.
You will pay for this!
You will be hanged!
You are going to pay for
everything you have done!
Bengi Hatun!
Speak everything you know, so that...
...the people can learn the truth.
Are they going to believe this liar?
You are going to tell the truth,
Bengi Hatun!
I will tell the truth.
I have no one else but
my daughter left in this world.
I swear on my daughter's life that...
...everything I say is the truth.
Ismihan made a plan against Malhun,
and wanted to make Osman lose his throne.
Bengi!
It was her that poisoned Orhan Bey...
...and spread a plague in Sogut!
There is not a single treachery
she wouldn't commit for power!
I know I made mistakes too.
I know.
I stood by her side despite knowing that.
I helped her in the crimes she committed.
I changed the silver of the coins
Osman Bey was going to make.
You traitor! You liar!
I did not do any of these!
You are evil!
The only thing you want is power!
Power poisons you..
...and you spread that poison around you!
You won't be able to spread your evil
in the border lands!
The trial is over.
The decision has been made!
Malhun Hatun is innocent.
Oh Allah, thank You.
Thank Allah.
Justice is served!
Mother Sultan!
Now it’s time.
It's time now, Mother Sultan!
You will be judged.
Soldiers!
Alps!
Allah is the Greatest!
Soldiers!
You will not let them pass!
You will die before
you let them open the gates!
Karabul. Celali.
Let’s go.
Oh Haqq!
Celali.
You know what to do.
Don't worry my Sultan.
Ismihan!
Ism i ha n!
Mother.
Orhan.
Orhan..
Alhamdulillah mother.
Allah knows I was very scared for you.
I didn't worry for a second.
I knew you were going to save me.
-Alaeddin.
-Mother Malhun.
Son.
Thank Allah Malhun.
Thank you.
We didn’t just save you
but ended Ismihan too.
Yes we did.
It's over this time.
She ran away from a hidden passage.
That snake.
Let her.
So she left huh?
We got rid of one more problem my bey.
InshAllah she won't come back.
Ill intended people never end
in these lands.
We can't just send away the insects.
We need to drain the swam
Gather around.
We're going to Konya.
Come on sons, come on.
The future of the nation is
in danger because of those Mongols.
Mongols are destroying it from the outside
and you from the inside.
You shouldn't have come to Konya.
If you want to save your life...
...leave Konya right away.
If not,
you're going to die like a traitor.
Let my life be sacrificed
for the future of Seljuk.
One can die but the nation lives on.
You commander Ertegin...
..how many times did we fight?
Unnumberable times!
What about you Commander Sungur?
Many times.
We all fight with you for all of Seljuk Sultan.
I know.
That's why I gathered you here.
What do you want from us?
My sultan...
...here.
What are these names Osman Bey?
There will be a fight soon.
These are the names of the commanders.
My sultan.
When I go to war...
...I don't want these commanders against me.
While the Sultan who owns
the throne is ordering them...
...who would listen to a Sultan
who was overthrown, Osman Bey?
No my sultan.
One of my best alps,
Konur will be with you.
Don't worry.
He went to war with
many of the commanders on this list.
Of course, everyone has a tough mission.
But if you stop a few
of the Mother Sultan's commanders...
..the rest will follow the truth.
We swung our swords
together at Konya for a while.
You know me...
...and I know you.
It is now a fight between
the right and the wrong.
Loyalty should only be shown
to the one who's following the truth.
Sultan Alaeddin and Imsihan Sultan
are working with Nayman.
How can a truthful man stand with them?
Do you have proof Konur?
Choose Sultan Mesut's
side before it's too late.
Everything will be revealed
once he's on the throne.
I want my throne back.
My throne...
...will be the savior of those being tortured
and the enemy of those who torture.
All of Seljuk...
...will have its old glory back.
It will be rid of...
...traitors.
Mother Sultan would end us.
That... That would mean the end for us.
Those who feed their sword with hatred...
...and those who say shahada in their last breath
will never end, commander Ertegin.
Besides..
...Osman Bey is with Sultan Mesut.
Osman Bey?
Yes you heard it right. Osman Bey.
He's going to end this with Sultan Mesut.
Tomorrow Osman Bey...
...will plan the last parts...
...of the plan near Cehennemdere.
I want to see you with him.
Beys.
On one side the real owner
of the throne Sultan Mesut..
...and Osman Bey...
...and the other side Mother Sultan
who works with the enemy.
Make your decision wisely.
Instead of reporting my uncle Mesut's
treachery, why didn't you kill him?
How did you let him be with his treachery?
My Sultan we wanted to tell you first.
He's your family.
Shut up.
I want that traitor dead.
His lust for the throne..
...will bring his end.
Send soldiers out Vizier.
We're going to find where he is.
Until my uncle is found
everywhere will be searched.
We will find Mesut.
Arid bring you his head my Sultan.
I won’t stop with his head.
I'm going to hang his body in front of Konya
so that everyone learns a lesson.
But not just him no.
I'm going to rip the heart of that...
...Osman who turns out to be behind everything.
You’ll go to Cehennemdere
as if you've betrayed me.
You're going to bring me Osman!
I will personally take Oman’s life.
Go on, get to work!
You've reached for the throne that's mine...
..and you shall pay.
I will be your nightmare!
Caravansarai.
Oh, Bengi!
You fool!
She messed everything up.
Everything!
She went behind my back!
But those who have crossed me..
...crosses the State of Seljuk as well.
Of course.
We're at your service, Mother Sultan.
Just give me the word and I'll kill her.
You will kill her.
You will.
No fault against the State of Seljuk
goes unpunished...
...but she can't get off that easy.
That won't be the case.
You're first going to make Bengi...
...feel tremendous pain.
You will kill Alcicek!
Then..
...you are going to kill Bengi.
Before she dies...
...I am going to make her experience
the greatest pain the world!
As you command Mother Sultan.
am going to kill both of them.
Rest assured.
I promised you power and unity.
But you betrayed me!
You will see what it means to...
...betray me, Bengi Hatun!
My Sultan, we got word
from Commander Ertegin.
Sultan Mesud is here..
...in Konya.
He is meeting the commanders
with the support of Osman Bey.
They are going to make the move...
..that would dethrone Sultan Alaeddin!
Send a messenger to Nayman.
As you command, Mother Sultan.
Bursa Palace.
Nayman...
...promised me Konya.
He told me that I am the man
that would revive Byzantine.
Is that possible?
Konya has been under the shadow
of Mongolians for years!
If we work together with Nayman
and fight against Gazan, and win the war...
...Konya will be ours.
We cannot put Byzantine into a battle like this
without asking Emperor Andronikos first.
That was his other offer.
When the battle is won, he told me that
I would sit on the throne of the empire.
After Gazan, Andronikos is next.
The council would want you to sit on the throne
more than anything, Lord Valens.
It's a dangerous decision no matter what.
We need to think carefully.
Our decision will change
the fate of Byzantine.
The enemy you know is better than
the one you don't know.
We have known Osman for years,
we can guess what he might do.
Osman is a simple man.
To Nayman, on the other hand,
we cannot trust.
Lord Valens!
Come in.
Sir, we got word from scouts.
Osman met dethroned Sultan near Konya.
Osman is going to dethrone Alaeddin
and enthrone Mesud.
Did you guess that too?
The soldiers that control this street,
which commander rules over them?
My Bey, that street and the soldiers in this street
are under commander Ertegin's command.
What about the city guards?
My Bey, Sultan Mesud is coming.
Let him come, come on.
Peace be with you.
Peace be upon you my Sultan.
Welcome. Come.
Thanks.
Brother.
I'll take it my Sultan.
Come in y Sultan.
Aykurt. Bring our Sultan food.
My Sultan.
InshAllah you have good news.
I have both good and bad news Osman Bey.
My Bey.
Some commanders
decided to side with us.
But almost half stayed with Mother Sultan.
Mother Sultan gave them promises.
But those who are oppressors...
...will always lose against us.
InshAllah my Bey.
My Sultan.
What about our other move?
We did as you said Osman Bey.
As Bayindir said...
...the commanders who are loyal to Ismihan,
Ertegi and Sungur...
...were told about the location you gave us.
They'll attack us there.
My Sultan.
They'll tell her about you.
It will be harder from now on.
So be it.
We're willing to die Osman Bey.
My Sultan.
This is the only way to win.
Thank you.
My Sultan.
Only tough people can walk the tough paths.
Eyvallah.
Let's begin.
You'll get back before nightfall.
-Eyvallah.
-Go ahead.
In the name of Allah.
Oktem's tribe
So dirty.
I can't get rid of this dirt.
It's not dirt, it's blood.
It's my blood on your hands.
You can’t wash away that blood.
Esma.
Esma forgive me.
Astagfirullah.
Allah forgive me.
Here my Sultan.
This is a crossroads.
This is how the game begins.
Now, Ertegin and Sungur must be
on their way to attack us.
They'thirtk they'll ambush you my Bey.
Now, our loyal commanders,
Salancu and Korkmaz...
...will arrest us when we get to Konya.
It's our men that will arrest you.
But the attackers..
..are Ismihan's followers.
This is how this game works.
Ismihan's followers will leave Konya.
And we will go to Konya with the Alps.
And InshAllah you’ll own the throne.
Mogol took my throne to help the Turks.
Then they fooled Ismihan and
used my nephew Alaeddin.
The captivity at the skirts of Konya
will come to an end too now.
Osman Bey.
When I get on the throne...
..I'll be supporting your dreams.
EyvAllah.
InshAllah the next time we see you...
...you'll be throned my Sultan.
First chains on my arms..,
..then the kaftan of sultanate on my back..
But...
...is the number of those commanders loyal to us enough?
There might be more in there.
Don't worry>
Once the swords are drawn..
...me and my alps will be with you.
We're going to get you on that throne.
Eyvallah.
Good luck to you.
Good luck to you too.
Be careful on the way.
Nayman's Base
We're going to go into the headquarters
with Mongolian clothes.
We'll enter the den of jackals
in their hide.
What will be Cerkutay's move?
We'll interfere within them.
Cerkutay will blow up the ammunition...
...and create chaos.
When the warriors go towards there...
...we're going to take the carriages out, huh?
You'll be able to handle it right?
Do your own work.
Come on.
Commander Nayman, Ismihan has sent this.
Osman.
Osman will weaken Ismihan.
The horses are running away.
-Horses are running away.. Quick!
-Bring water.
Come on. Come on.
-Run! Run!
-They're running.
It's coming this way come on.
Be quick. Come on.
Come on. Come on.
-Brother...
-Hurry up!
...let's go.
Hurry up!
Watch out!
Come on!
Hurry up, everyone!
Let's go, brother.
Bring more water here?
Let's go, brothers.
They're taking the catapults!
Gurbuz!
Where's Gurbuz, brother?
Run, brother!
Take my hand, brother!
Brother!
Stop them!
Come on, brother!
Come on!
Brother!
Shoot him!
Come on-
Brother!
Stop the carriage!
Leave me.
Leave me and take the catapults.
Hang in there!
Let's go.
Let's go!
We're leaving, brother!
Shoot the mighty arrows of the Turks, my lions!
Bring order with your bows!
Oh, Haqq!
Alright, Gurbuz.
You did the right thing.
But I stumbled upon many wrong paths...
...until I found the right one.
I even have my own family's
blood on my hands.
Don't blame yourself for Esma’s death.
You didn’t know Ismihan
could have gone that far.
I'm afraid she'll go even further now.
She threatened me with Alcicek's life.
Don't let Alcicek leave
your sight, Aktemur.
Don't worry, mother. Trust m
I will protect Alcicek
and our tribe with my life.
What's going on here?
What are you two whispering about?
Is there a problem?
There's no problem.
I just needed Aktemur Bey's
opinion on some issues.
Hang in there...brother.
Hang in there.
We're almost there.
We're about to get to Yenisehir!
Go faster!
Hurry up!
Hang in there.
We'll get to Yenisehir and you'll be fine.
Faster!
The doctors there will help you,
hang in there!
Hang in there, brother!
Hang in there!
On my mark!
One, two, three!
-Alright.
-Faster!
Hang in there.
Hold on! Look at me!
You are okay!
You are okay! You will be okay!
Come on!
Faster!
Brother! Faster!
You are going to eat all the food by yourself, Gurbuz.
You are going to eat all the food by yourself.
Faster! Come on!
When we kill Osman,
Mother Sultan will make us very rich.
How richer can Mother Sultan
make you Commander Ertegin?
Ertegi’s loyalty is expensive.
Well, you are not cheap either,
we love money too. Let's go take Osman.
Commander Salancu,
we found Mesut's location.
We entered the house our eyes closed,
how did you find it?
We told them about what we heard.
With the skill of our soldiers,
it was not hard.
You are a good commander.
Then you will take Mesud, and we will take Osman.
Today, blood will be spilled in Konya.
The blood to be spilled
will make us rich.
The coin brought by blood
will only take you to hell.
Bengi Hatun.
Welcome.
Why are you here, Mother Ayse?
For our duty.
We will take Bengi Hatun to trial.
I was waiting for you.
Come on, let's go.
What are you saying, aunt Malhun?
My mother risked her life and
told everything that Ismihan Sultan did.
Instead of thanking me,
are you going to punish me?
We are grateful.
She helped us.
But her confession does not redeem her crimes.
No.
I won't let you.
I just have my mother left.
We will go far away if necessary,
but I won’t let her go.
Alcicek.
It's just a trial.
If my mother goes, I will not forgive you.
Alcicek.
You are being an obstacle to the justice.
Don’t do this, my girl.
I know what I did,
and the punishment for it.
Now move.
Let it happen, okay?
There is no need for that.
Here.
This is yours now.
May Allah protect you.
Take care of each other.
Be careful.
Don't worry.
We'll protect Alcicek.
Thanks Ayse Hatun.
Come on.
Come here. Come here.
You thought we'd betray Mother Sultan, Osman Bey?
We're only loyal to Mother Sultan.
She gave us this power.
Mother Sultan's followers..
...are betraying the state.
Mother Sultan..
...knows nothing but herself and her power.
Now...
...you can choose the right side.
The only owner of the throne...
..is Sultan Mesut.
You think you can get away with it Osman Bey?
This is your last rebellion.
Now we'll take you
to Mother Sultan...
..and increase .our gold.
Great Seljuk's powerful commanders!
Foolishness..
...is a deep pit.
I know it well.
When you fall..
...it's hard to get out.
We're trying to help you, friends.
Don't do it.
Don't be blinded.
Choose the right side.
So, you’re a part of the treason Bayindir Bey.
No.
Alhamdulillah.
...have chosen the right side.
You trapped us Osman Bey.
This only proves you're a traitor.
We know where Konur and Mesut are.
They're dead.
Is that so?
Come on th
Attack!
Mother Sultan's commanders
are going to Osman now.
Can we trust the ones in here Sultan Hadrath?
We can't trust anyone now.
They can change sides.
Your life must be worth a lot Sultan Hadrath.
No one's coin was enough until now.
Let's see whom destiny has in store for us.
At least..
...our side and fight are clear.
EyvAllah.
But know this..
...if someone's going to die,
it will be me first.
You won't fall before I do.
Eyvallah.
The traitor Mesut..
...and his helper Konur.
You're under arrest. Take them.
Now..
..you think you tricked us is that so?
But from the very start we knew
you were loyal to Mother Sultan.
If there's..
...someone who will set up a trap...
...then it's just us.
Mother Sultan will make you pay for this.
Mesut and Konur must be dead already, Osman.
What difference our deaths will make?
Do you know why I called you here?
Why?
There is..
...no commander left in Konya
who is loyal to...
...Ismihan Sultan.
The commanders who are in Konya..
...are just loyal to Sultan Mesut.
...by coming here from Konya
you left Mother Sultan alone.
Bayindir.
Take them to the cave with Huseyin.
After Sultan Mesut sits on the throne
he will decide what will happen to them.
As you wish my bey.
Go to Mother Sultan.
Continue your duty.
Yes.
Move.
What happened?
What is her punishment?
Aunt in law?
Mother?
Judge...
...has given Bengi Hatun two years in exile.
She will be staying in the dungeon until she leaves.
Mother.
Girl.
Don t cry.
Don t cry my beautiful girl.
My beautiful girl.
Don't be mad at me.
Come on.
-Come on.
-Alcicek.
My Sultan...
...here are the traitors who laid eyes
on your throne and planned bloody moves.
Your traitor uncle Mesud and Osman’s Alp Konur.
Uncle..
...why did you do this to me?
I always wanted you to live.
I had nothing against you.
My only concern has always been
the longevity of our State.
Do you see the situation, mother?
I do, Hadrat Sultan.
I do.
I had brought...
...my personal guards here...
..in case traitor Osman and...
...Mesud, who has eyes on your throne,
would do something.
But it seems the guards weren't necessary.
Mesut...
Instead of waiting for a peaceful death in your cell...
...you allowed Osman to use you in his plans.
You've damaged the State of Seljuk!
You..
Do you think working with Nayman...
...and going against the Turks
and Islam benefits the State?
What about you, Alaeddin?
Do you think that..
...letting your mother always control you
is the way to be the Sultan?
You are collaborating with Mongolians,
the people...
...whom we fought for centuries to stay free!
But why?
Why do you think?
It's because of their hatred towards Osman Bey.
Your Osman Bey...
...does not even deserve our hate!
Look at what you’ve done!
Look at what you’ve caused!
Your anger blinded you in such a way that
you work with our enemy.
How many valiants did Nayman kill?
-Enough!
-Mother Sultan.
There's someone who wants to see you.
Mother Sultan.
We’ve identified all the places
where Osman might be hiding at in Konya
Each are toeing watched.
I'm waiting to hear from them.
So don't worry.
I will bring him to you
as soon as possible.
Find them immediately, Bayindir.
They will continue to breathe until then.
Can I come in?
Come in.
Mother Sultan, my Bey.
We found Osman.
Mother Sultan Hadrath, allow me to..
...bring that last traitor to you.
If you come empty handed, Bayindir...
...I am going to put you in prison with them.
I am going to hang them all in Konya square.
No one will be able to..
...think about rebelling.
Be quick Bayind
Every breath they take harms us.
Cavundur's Bayindir.
Try to trick me...
...and I will make you experience
the greatest of pains!
Alps! Bring a stretcher!
Kumral Abdal! Kara Ebe!
Cerkutay?
What happened?
Gurbuz Alp!
Alps! Find Kumral Abdal quickly!
Kara Ebe! Kara Ebe!
Kara Ebe!
Help! My brother is dying!
Slowly.
His wound looks deep,
carry him inside quickly.
We need to cauterize the wound.
Allah protect him!
Oh Allah protect him
You are okay brother.
Inside! Quickly!
-You will be okay!
-Stop Cerkutay.
Stop.
My time has come
No! No!
No, no!
Give me your blessing.
No! You are going to eat more food with me!
Not now, brother.
I bear witness that there's none
worthy of worship except Allah...
...and I also bear witness that Mohammad
is His servant and messenger.
Am I dead?
Wait.
It's time for the questioning.
I am really dead, the questioning has begun.
Tell me, Gurbuz.
Who is your Lord?
Oh Allah, help me.
Great Allah.
Brother Gurbuz..
...what's your religion?
My religion is Islam.
I am sorry.
You look familiar.
And I don’t feel dead.
Is this how dead people see others?
This is just a disguise.
Now, you are going to answer
for the apples you stole from Cerkutay.
Apples?
Apples? What apples?
Cerkutay gave me his blessing.
Did he not?
Let me check.
It's written here.
He did not.
The apple is the cause? Am I going to hell?
Gurbuz Alp.
You should have thought about
that before eating haram food.
Cerkutay, just for an apple?
You ruined me!
May the apples you ate be halal for you,
I will give you the whole tree if you want brother.
Come on get up.
Am I dead?
Am I alive?
You did not die.
Cerkutay.
I'll kill you.
You will. You will. Just lie down.
Get some rest and get better.
Take this and go to bed.
Then you can kill me.
This is good.
Get some rest. Come on brother.
Let's get back to duty.
In the name of Allah.
I didn't die.
They'll be here soon.
Huseyin.
Did you do as I said?
We did my Bey.
Good.
Allah forbid...
I don't want any mistakes.
They're here.
My Bey.
Everything’s ready as you said.
But...
Ismihan.
She found a unit full of the best soldiers of Seljuk.
This unit is waiting by the Sultan.
They're waiting'for us.
What about Sultan Mesut and Konur? Ar
They're okay for now. But my Bey...
When I told them I had you..
...Ismihan said she would kill them
in the city center.
They're waiting for us.
Then when I go to Ismihan..
...it will be a tough fight.
Are you afraid?
No my Bey.
AstagfiruIlah.
My only fear is to choose the wrong side.
I'm willing to die for the right one.
Eyvallah.
Come on. Give the Alps the clothes.
Tie up our hands.
Here.
In the name of Allah.
What a shame.
You used to
Now you're waiting to die here.
You used to rule this city.
Now you'll die here.
Mesut.
What about you?
Osman's Alp...
Konur..
You grew up in Great Seljuk...
...and commanded
the Viziers of the city.
Now you'll die here.
Who got you here?
Osman Bey did.
In a short time...
....he'll join you.
Osman Bey?
We don't fear death.
Maybe you'll live longer than us.
Once I kill you..
..I'll have a lot of time to think.
Don't worry at all Mesut.
What is it?
Commanders?
Are you disturbed?
It's not our place Mother Sultan.
Whatever you order is the rule.
Your word is our order.
I thought so too.
...there are a lot of executioners in Konya.
Sultan..
...there's word from Bayindir.
Osman.
He caught him.
Finally.
Send the town criers.
A lot of blood wi be spilled today
Take them away.
I was defeated by my nafs.
I became one of those who make mistakes.
Forgive this sinner servant of yours Allah...
Ameen.
Mother.
Alcicek..
Daughter...
Forgive me.
I couldn't protect you.
You should forgive me.
While I was making a mistake
I made you follow me.
Don't be like me okay?
Don't fall for your greed girl.
My flower.
Sultan Alaeddin Han..
..and Mother Ismihan Sultan.
I present to you,
the leader of traitors...
...Osman Bey.
Remove your hands!
Remove them!
At last! All traitors..
...are present in front of me...
...waiting to die together.
At last!
My Sultan.
Osman Bey...
Did you betray me because
I refused to give you soldiers?
Sultan Alaeddin..
..there's only one reason for all of this.
What is it?
I'd like to hear that before you die.
You worked with the enemy..
...to save yourself.
An enemy that...
...killed many brave men..
...and took many innocent lives!
My Sultan...
...you didn’t do anything about
all the evil plans...
...Mother Sultan made.
She took many innocent lives..
...spread disease over my lands...
...poisoned my son...
...imprisoned my Hatun...
...betrayed the Turks...
...and betrayed Islam!
But still..
...she is going to pay for what
she has done.
-If you're done telling lies--Mother.
Is anything true about...
...what Osman Bey said?
You should never listen to the
rebels who are after your throne...
..my Sultan..
...as they speak nothing but lies...
...and I've had enough!
The traitors will die today!
Look at that!
Hadrat Mother Sultan..
..once Osman here dies..
...will you let me keep his sword?
I don't care about it, Bayindir.
You really got used to giving away...
...things that aren't yours, Ismihan Hatun.
Just like the throne!
Isn't that right. Bayindir?
It doesn't belong to them,
yet she tries to share it with others.
Both the sword and the word..
...is Osman Bey's!
Oh, Allah!
Alps!
The throne is now Sultan Mesud's!
Alaeddin..
...surrender the throne without further bloodshed.
There is no surrender without bloodshed, Mesud!
You're all going to die today!
But you, Bayindir...
Yours is the greatest of betrayals.
Your death will not be easy.
And of course...
...not realizing such a great betrayal...
...happening in front of my eyes..
...would make me nothing but a fool.
Osman.
Visit our website for more: turkision.com